One hell of a vacation.
Alarum is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Michael Polish.
Two married spies caught in the crosshairs of an international intelligence
network will stop at nothing to obtain a critical asset.
Joe and Lara are agents living off the grid whose quiet retreat at a winter resort is blown to shreds when members
of the old guard suspect the two may have joined an elite team of rogue spies, known as Alarum.
Joe Travers, played by Scott Eastwood.
Chester, played by Sylvester Stallone.
Lara Travers, played by Willa Fitzgerald.
Orlin, played by Mike Colter.
Ronald Burbridge, played by D.W. Moffett.
Bridgette Rousseau, played by Isis Valverde.
Alarum is a 2025 American action crime thriller film directed by Michael Polish and starring Scott
Eastwood, Sylvester Stallone, Willa Fitzgerald, Mike Colter, Ísis Valverde, and Joel Cohen.
In this film, Joe and Lara who were once rivals, fall in love
during a mission and decide to go rogue to get married.
They manage to escape their respective agencies and establish a quiet life, but their peace is shattered
when a plane crash near their cabin reveals a hard drive that several organizations want.
Alarum was released in the United States in select theaters
and on video on demand on January 17, 2025.
The film explores themes of assassin, spy, married
couple, secret organization, shootout.
The tone is intense.